dealspl.us 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - DealsPlus

Here at DealsPlus we recognize that your privacy is very important, and to keep you informed about our privacy practices we ask that you please read the guidelines described below. Keep in mind that because DealsPlus is a growing website and internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change and any said changes will be posted on this page. Any material changes from current practices will be posted here to serve as notice. DealsPlus is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which it may link.

### Legal Basis for Processing

We have the legal right to use your Personal Information in the ways described in this Privacy Policy based on your consent, or on the need to use the Personal Information to provide you with goods or services that you request, or for the legitimate purposes of furthering our existing relationship with you or preventing fraud. Accordingly, you have a contractual rather than a statutory obligation to provide such information. If you do not provide such information, you may be unable to use our Services and we may be unable to provide any goods or services that you request.

### Personal Information

During registration for membership, we may collect personal information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, tax payer information, PayPal account information, blockchain wallet information and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for more information. We usually collect personal information directly from you although sometimes we may use agents or service providers to do this for us. When you are online, we collect information regarding the pages within our network that you visit. We may also acquire lists from other sources, both from other companies and from other public documents. For each visitor on our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We do not collect personal information on consumers who browse our website without an account but we may collect information related to their clickstream, the retailers they visit and the products they interact with on our site or on the websites of the merchants they visit.

### Use of Aggregate Data

We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our website for your computer (e.g., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address, unique device identifiers, device or session IDs and connected hardware (e.g., computer or mobile device) and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our website. DealsPlus may use personally identifiable information in aggregate form to improve our goods and services, including our website, and to make them more responsive to the needs of our customers. This statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by DealsPlus, or provided to others as a summary report for marketing, advertising, or research purposes.

### Location Information

Use of our mobile application may, at your election, include location-based services. When you use the app, you may transmit information about your location to DealsPlus. That information will be used to offer you deals and coupons that are close to your geographic location.

### Use of Information

We use your information to provide our services to you, to fulfill administrative functions associated with these services, to enter into contracts with you or third parties, to improve our services, to administer contests or sweepstakes, and for marketing and client relationship purposes. You may receive e-mails from us to let you know about new products, services, and upcoming events that may interest you. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us or you want to make changes to your e-mail settings, please change your setting under your setting tab. We will never sell or distribute your e-mail address to other companies or organizations, and your account password will always remain protected. We may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes here to notify you of these changes, and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check our Privacy Policy periodically.

### Affiliated Companies; Business Transfers

We may disclose Personal Information to our subsidiaries and affiliates. We may share the information we collect, including Personal Information, with any third party in connection with, or during negotiations of, any proposed or actual merger, purchase, sale (including a liquidation, realization, foreclosure, or repossession), or any other type of acquisition of all or any portion of DealsPlus assets, conveyance or transfer of all or a portion of our business to another company.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site, and they allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. But you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as merchandise transactions, DP Credit or registered services.

### Analytics, Targeting, Tracking

We, and third parties with which we partner, may also use cookies, pixels, and other technologies to automatically collect information about your use of the Services, such as your click-stream data, IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversion information. Data collected from a particular browser or device may be used with another computer or device that is linked to the browser or device on which such data was collected (also known as cross-linking). We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign on other websites or platforms. These third parties may also collect Personal Information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Services to help predict your preferences and to display (and to enable other third parties to display) ads to be more likely to be of interest to you. Some third-party service providers that we engage (including third-party retailers and advertisers) may also place their own cookies on your browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties.

###  Use of Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track and analyze certain traffic and usage statistics regarding our customers’ use of our Services, such as number of visitors using our Services, how visitors are navigating to our Services, visitors’ general geographic region information, how long our visitors are visiting our Services, and information about the equipment our visitors are using to access the Services, such as browser version and operating system. Google Analytics may use a Google Analytics cookie and may collect your IP address as part of this service (but neither we nor Google Analytics otherwise collects or processes any of your Personal Information in connection with our use of the Google Analytics services). We use this traffic and usage information to gauge, internally, the effectiveness of our advertising efforts and to make improvements the Services. 

In addition, with respect to the our websites only, we use the following Google Analytics Advertising Features: 

  * Remarketing
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Google Ads (an integrated service with Google Analytics)

By enabling these features, Google collects certain additional traffic and usage data using a Google Advertising cookie and other identifiers not tied to your Personal Information. This information includes demographic information about our website visitors and general information about our visitors’ interests, but does not identify our visitors individually. In fact, we are prohibited by Google policy from using this information to try to identify individual users or for merging non-personally-identifiable information obtained from Google with personally-identifiable information we otherwise have about you without obtaining your separate consent. We use the information collected from our use of the Google Analytics Advertising Features to segment our audience and better target our ad campaigns (for example, to target 26-34 year old visitors with certain ads in Google search results that have previously shown a high degree of success in the 26-34 year old visitor demographic).

For more information, please review the following: 

  * Information about Google’s use of Google Analytics cookies and Google Advertising cookies: https://policies.google.com/technologies/types
  * How Google uses information from sites or apps that use Google’s services: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

You can opt-out of our use of certain Google Analytics features by updating the Ad Settings in your browser (http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or mobile device (https://support.google.com/ads/answer/1660762#mob), by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s (NAI’s) Consumer Opt-Out page at http://optout.networkadvertising.org/", or by visiting Google’s currently available opt-outs over the web at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

### Referral Programs

We may offer features which allow you to inform an individual about our Services. If you choose to use our referral features, we will ask you for your referral’s email address to send them an electronic communication inviting them to join our Services. We will store this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of our referral program. If you choose to participate in our referral programs, you represent and warrant that you have a personal relationship with your referral and that you are authorized to share their information with us for the purpose of sending this communication to invite them to join the Services. 

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary in order to provide products or services to you. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our website.

###  Rights Applicable to Certain Users

EU Users

If you are visiting from the European Union (“EU”) or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from EU or United States law, please note that you may be transferring your Personal Information to us in the United States and in other countries around the world for the purposes described under this Privacy Policy. Please note that the EU has determined that the laws of the United States do not provide adequate protection for your Personal Information. Accordingly, we are transferring your Personal Information from the EU to the United States based on your consent, or our need to use your Personal Information to provide goods or services that you order, and subject to the following additional protections:

If we intend to disclose your Personal Information to any third party that will carry out processing on our behalf, we will enter into a contract with that third party that provides that your Personal Information may be processed only for limited and specified purposes consistent with the consent that you have provided to us, and that the third party must provide the same level of protection for your Personal Information that we are obligated to provide under this Policy while it is processing your Personal Information.

If your Personal Information is being processed by automated means, you have the right to obtain a copy of your provided Personal Information, together with certain additional Personal Information that we have generated as a result of your use of our services, in a structured and commonly used and machine-readable format, and to transfer such Personal Information to another service provider. Upon your request, we will transfer that Personal Information directly to another service provider if it is feasible for us to do so.

If we are processing your Personal Information based on your consent, you may withdraw that consent at any time. 

You may restrict our use of your Personal Information, by sending us an email stating your request to support@DealsPlus.com, if you have contested the accuracy of that information, or if the processing is unlawful or you need the information to establish, exercise or defend a legal claim. We will then store your Personal Information and process it only with your consent, or to establish, exercise or defend a legal claim or to protect the rights of others. The restriction with respect to information claimed to be inaccurate would end if we verify the accuracy of that contested information.

Upon our receipt of your request by email at support@DealsPlus.com and our verification of your identity, we will advise you whether or not we are processing Personal Information concerning you and, if so, we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information being processed and certain information about the nature and purposes of the processing. If your Personal Information is used for automated decision-making, we will provide you with information on the logic being used and the types of decisions being made. You may correct any such Personal Information that is inaccurate or incomplete. 

Upon your request, we will erase any of your Personal Information that is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was collected, or that is being used for direct marketing purposes, or if our use is based on your consent and you withdraw that consent.

Our Services may be used by children in the EU between the ages of 13 and 16 only with parental consent. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child in the EU under the age of 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

If we are using your Personal Information on the basis of your consent, and we change our Privacy Policy to permit any use or disclosure of your Personal Information that is materially different than the uses for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you, we will obtain your consent before we make such further uses of your Personal Information.

If you have a complaint about our compliance with this Policy, you may contact us at support@DealsPlus.com. If you are not satisfied with our response, you will have the right to lodge a complaint with the Supervisory authority in your country of residence in the EU.

If you are not subject to EU law, these rights do not apply to you.

California Residents

If you are a California resident, you may (i) obtain certain information regarding our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and/or (ii) at any time opt-out of receiving promotional communications from us and/or request that we discontinue providing any of your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties, in each case by sending an email to support@DealsPlus.com. Please note that if you decide to opt-out of receiving promotional information or request that we discontinue providing your Personal Information, your change in preference will only affect future contacts; if the information already has been provided to third parties, they may continue to use it.

Children

Our Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age, and no one under age 13 may provide any information to the Services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under age 13, do not use or provide any information to the Services, make any purchases through the Services, use any of the interactive or public comment features of the Services, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, phone number, email address or any screen name or username you may use. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at support@DealsPlus.com.

### Your Choices

You may in some cases have the option to decline providing us information. However, your choice to not provide information may impact your use of certain features or services. You may unsubscribe or opt out of receiving marketing communications from us by using the unsubscribe link on the footer of our marketing emails or by using the Contact Us option through the Services. We encourage you to maintain the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as the information you provide us to register for your account. The Services may allow you to access, review, correct, update, and remove or make inaccessible Personal Information you have provided through your account settings. You may provide account updates and changes by logging into your account and changing settings or by using the Contact Us option through the Services. With respect to our mobile and other applications, you can prospectively stop all collection of information by the application by uninstalling the application. We will make good-faith efforts to make requested changes in our then-active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. 

### What else you should know about privacy on the Internet

  * Remember to close your browser when you have finished your DealsPlus session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place, like a library or internet cafe. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer.
  * Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information over the internet, this information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information in publicly accessible online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
  * Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username and passwords and any account information.
  * Please be careful and responsible whenever you are using the internet.

_If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or you would like to cancel your account, please contact us at support@dealsplus.com_
